⊠ mmichellekimm@gmail.com

(714) 931-6595

@ michellekim.design

Projects

RUMBLE

Restaurant decision-making app - iOS mobile application

Conceptualized a restaurant decision-making app helping users from indecision. Conducted user research to understand the user and create user stories to translate into wireframes and mockups. Conducted user testing to iterate my designs and established a brand identity.

MENTORUP

Used design thinking to create a solution to a challenge specific to the South LA community.

Worked as a team to create a mentorship program consisting of letters and custom resource packages, connecting those currently incarcerated with mentors to help them acclimate back into society. Contributed to research, creating user journeys and branding.

CLOUDROP

Saas cloud storage application allowing users to create and save content.

Created solutions for a cluttered and hard-to-navigate cloud storage site. Conducted research through surveys and user interviews, created user stories, wireframes and hi-fi mockups, and established a brand identity through moodboards and a style guide.

Experience

JoinBorrow- UX Design Intern

A short-term electric car subsciption service startup.

Redesigning the company's website through user feedback, building brand identity, and marketing ads through various digital channels.

Los Angeles, CA | MAR 2019 - Present (Part-time)

BLOC.IO- Design Program

Studied and applied design principles and frontend development to web and mobile application projects under the mentorship of 2 senior UX professionals. I worked on capstone projects from conceptualization to finalization. I also designed and developed a personal portfolio using HTML, CSS and Javascript.

Los Angeles, CA / Remote | DEC 2017 - MAR- 2019

EPIK- English Teacher

Daegu, South Korea | MAR 2016 - MAR 2017

Skills

TOOLS

Sketch Illustrator Figma
Invision Marvel Whimsical

CODING

HTML CSS Javascript

UX METHODS

Sketching / Wireframing User Surveys
User Stories Interviews
Competitive Analysis Prototyping
Site Maps & User Flows User Personas
Journey Maps

Education

University of California, Santa Barbara

BA, International Studies Minor in Spanish and Psychology

Santa Barbara, CA | JULY 2011- JUNE 2015

Universitat Autonoma de Barcelona

UCEAP Full Immersion Program BA, Interculteral Communications

Barcelona, Spain | AUG 2013 - JUNE 2014

Languages

Spanish - Fluent Korean - Proficient